A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Program and Policy, SG 3.5 FA1843
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program and Policy - General, 900; 89.85 Cubic Feet 233 containers
  - Program and Policy - General (No program letter)
    - Program and Policy - Strategy Development - Suburban Property, 2013 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Sustainable Employment in a Green U.S. Economy (SEGUE), 2009-2013 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Synergy Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Task Force on Development, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 4-5, Box 189, Folder 1-3, Box 190, Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Task Force on Development, 1986 (Box 191, Folder 2-4, Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Task Force on Development, 1984 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Task Force on Development, 1986-1987 (Box 192, Folder 3-4)
    - Program and Policy - Task Force on Development, 1986-1987 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Terrorism, 2001 (Box 192, Folder 5, Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Transitions to Growth, 2011 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Transportation Initiative, 2008-2010 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Transportation Initiative, 2011-2014 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Transportation Initiative, 2011-2014 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Undercapitalized Slum Economies, 2013-2014 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas, 1984-2000 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - History, 1977-1980 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - History, 1981-1983 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - History, 1984 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - History - Supplementary Material (Box 196, Folder 2, Box 197, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Urban Coastal Zones, 2013-2014 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Urban Financing Innovation, 2008-2014 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Urban Financing Innovation, 2008-2014 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Program and Policy - Urban Management Challenges, 2012 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Waste and Spoilage, 2013 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Vaccinations, 1984-1985 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Vaccinations, 1984-1985 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Program and Policy - Women, 2001 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Weather and Climate, 2007 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Urban Policy, 1992 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Workers in the Informal Economy, 2013 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities, 1999-2001 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities - Trip Reports, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities, 2002-2003 (Box 200, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities, 2004-2005 (Box 200, Folder 4, Box 201, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities, 2006-2008 (Box 201, Folder 3, Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities, 2006-2008 (Box 179, Folder 8)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2079
    - Program and Policy - Working Communities - Supplementary Material (Box 202, Folder 2)
      Commission for a New Social Contract
    - Program and Policy - Year 2000 Compliance, 1992-1999 (Box 202, Folder 3, Box 203, Folder 1, Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Year 2000 Compliance, 1992-1999 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Year 2000 Compliance - Supplementary Material (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Seal (Minutes), 2003-2007 (Box 203, Folder 3-4, Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Seal, 1998-2013 (Box 204, Folder 3, Box 206, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Seal - Supplementary Material (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx), 1996-1998 (Box 357, Folder 5, Box 358, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx), 1999-2001 (Box 358, Folder 4-5, Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx), 2002-2004 (Box 359, Folder 2-5, Box 360, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx), 2005 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx) - Front of File, 1996-2005 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx) - Minutes, 1996-2001 (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx) - Supplementary Material (Box 361, Folder 1-5, Box 362, Folder 1-4, Box 363, Box 364)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx) - Supplementary Material (Box 365, Folder 1-5, Box 366, Box 367, Folder 1-3, Box 368)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx) - Meeting, 2004-2006 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx), 1998-2000 (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Program Related Investments (PRI Fund), 1984-1996 (Box 369, Folder 3, Box 370, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Program Related Investments (PRI Fund), 1997-2013 (Box 370, Folder 3-5, Box 371, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Program Related Investments - Supplementary Material, 1984-1996 (Box 371, Folder 3-5)
    - Program and Policy - Social Investing, 2007-2011 (Box 372, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Resilience, 2011-2013 (Box 372, Folder 4, Box 373, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Resilience, 2013-2014 (Box 374, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - Resilience, 2013-2014 (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Poverty Reduction through Information and Digital Employment (PRIDE), 2010-2013 (Box 374, Folder 3-4, Box 376, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Poverty Reduction through Information and Digital Employment (PRIDE), 2014 (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Poverty Reduction through Information and Digital Employment (PRIDE), 2014 (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative - Front of File, 2008-2016 (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative, 2008-2009 (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative, 2009-2010 (Box 376, Folder 3, Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative, 2010-2012 (Box 377, Folder 2-4, Box 378, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative, 2013-2016 (Box 378, Folder 2-3)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative - Supplementary Material (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative - Trip Reports, 2008-2013 (Box 379, Folder 1-4)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative - Trip Reports, 2012-2014 (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Health Systems Initiative - Team Retreat, 2008 June (Box 380, Folder 1-2)
    - Program and Policy - China, 1980-1985 (Box 380, Folder 4-6)
    - Program and Policy - China, 1986-2005 (Box 381, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - China, 1986-2005 (Box 375, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2076
    - Program and Policy - Officers Meetings, 2001 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy - Confidential materials - Program Reviews, 1989-2008 (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - Grants, Programs, and Expenditures, 1983-1992 (Box 390, Folder 2-4, Box 391, Folder 1-3)
  - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Programs, 900E
    - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Programs, 1977-1998 (Box 207, Folder 1-3)
    - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Programs, 1998-2012 (Box 207, Folder 4, Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, 1998-2012 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards - Supplementary Material (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Evaluation, 1973-1991 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - History, 1978-1989 (Box 209, Folder 2-3)
    - History, 1978-1989 (Box 205, Folder 3)
      Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2060
    - Immigration, 1971-2003 (Box 209, Folder 4, Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Medical Care, 1970-1981 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Place of Study, 1970-1994 (Box 208, Folder 3-4)
    - Place of Study - Contributions to Institutions, 1994-1996 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Place of Study - Contributions to, 1969-1974 (Box 213, Folder 3-4)
    - Place of Study - Contributions to, 1975-1980 (Box 214, Folder 1-2)
    - Place of Study - Contributions to, 1981-1983; 1993 (Box 214, Folder 3, Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Survey - Fellows, 1979, 1992 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Stipend - Taxation, 1970-1980 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Stipend, 1970-1993 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships, 1988-1989 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships, 1988-1989 (Box 205, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2029
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships, 1990-1995 (Box 211, Folder 2, Box 212, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2035
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships, 1996-1998 (Box 212, Folder 2)
      Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2038
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - A-B, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 5-6, Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - B-C, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 1-2)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - C-G, 1989 (Box 217, Folder 1-2)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - H-K, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 1-2)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - K-M, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 1-2)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - N-P, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 1-2, Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - Q-U, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 2, Box 222, Folder 1-2)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - V-Z, 1989 (Box 223, Folder 1-2, Box 224)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - Reports, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - Reports, 1994-1999; 2007 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Warren Weaver Fellowships - Scene of Change, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 1)
- Charter, Constitution and By-Laws, 902; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Charter, Constitution and By-Laws, 1962-2014 (Box 226, Folder 2-4)
- Members and Meetings, 903; 5.79 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1960-1972 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1964-1974 (Box 228, Folder 1-2)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1975-1978 (Box 227, Folder 2, Box 228, Folder 3-4)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1979-1982 (Box 227, Folder 3-4, Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1983-1984 (Box 229, Folder 2-4)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1984-1989 (Box 230, Folder 1-3)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1990-1998 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 1999-2002 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 2003-2006 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Executive Officers - Open in 2034
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees), 2007-2013 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Members and Meetings (Executives, Trustees) - Supplementary Material (Box 232, Folder 1-3, Box 233, Folder 1-2)
  - Members and Meetings - Supplementary Material - Trustees Photographs, 1998-2016 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Executive Officers - Open in 2037
  - Members and Meetings - Asia Trip, 2000 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Members and Meetings - Asia Trip, 2000 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Members and Meetings - Audit Committee, 2002-2006 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Members and Meetings - Bellagio Meetings - Board of Trustees, 1984-1999, 2005 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Members and Meetings - Candidates, 1971-1994 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Members and Meetings - Candidates, 1971-2003 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Members and Meetings - Committee on Trusteeship, 2001-2003 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Members and Meetings - Dockets and Minutes, 1960-1999 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Members and Meetings - Dockets and Minutes, 1960-1999 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Members and Meetings - East Africa Trip, 1989 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Members and Meetings - Eastern and Southern African Trip, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Members and Meetings - Eastern and Southern African Trip, 1997 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2068
  - Members and Meetings - Harlem Tour, 1990 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Members and Meetings - India/Indonesia Trip, 1993-1994 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Members and Meetings - Manuals, 1994-2001 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Members and Meetings - Manuals, 2002 (Box 237, Folder 1-2)
  - Members and Meetings - Nominating Committee, 1960-1976 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Members and Meetings - Nominating Committee, 1977-1991 (Box 238, Folder 1-2)
  - Members and Meetings - Mexico Trip, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Members and Meetings - Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Members and Meetings - Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Members and Meetings - Pocantico Retreat, 2000 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Members and Meetings - 2002 Boston Trip (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Members and Meetings - 2002 Thailand and Vietnam Trip (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies, 1972-1973 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Members and Meetings - 2004 Vietnam Trip (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - Members and Meetings - 2004 Thailand Trip (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - Members and Meetings - 2007 Thailand Trip (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Members and Meetings - Uganda Trip, 2002 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Members and Meetings - 2004 Kenya/Uganda Trip (Box 241, Folder 3-4)
  - Members and Meetings - 2004 Kenya/Uganda Trip (Box 239, Folder 2)
- Officers Diaries, 905; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - LAS, 1985-1987 (Box 386, Folder 4)
- Insurance, Medical Care and Personnel, 909; 8.36 Cubic Feet 22 letter document boxes
  - Personnel, 1985-2006 (Box 239, Folder 3-4, Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Supplementary Material (Box 242, Folder 2-3, Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Manual, 1971-1995 (Box 243, Folder 2-3)
  - Insurance - Personnel - Reports, c. 1919-1980 (Box 244, Folder 1-2)
  - Insurance - Liability, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Salaries, 1951-1989 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Salaries, 1990-2004 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Severance, 1949-2006 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Tuition, c. 1990 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Holidays and Vacations, c. 1984 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Employment and Procedures, c. 1999 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - Overtime, c. 1960 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Personnel - Insurance - General, c. 2017 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Group Life Insurance, 1923-2009 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Personnel - Group Life Insurance - Minutes, 1919-1982 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Provident Fund (India), 1967 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Personnel - Dental Insurance, 1957-1997 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Retirement, 1919-1984 (Box 248, Folder 1-2)
  - Personnel - Retirement, 1985-2012 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Retirement - Minutes, c. 1985 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Retirement - Supplementary Material, 1919-1984 (Box 250, Folder 1, Box 251)
  - Personnel - Medical Care - Reports, c. 1963 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Immunization, 1970-1981 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Thrift Incentive Plan, 1967-1997 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - State Planning, c. 1972 (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Consultants, 1965-2009 (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee, 1975-2017 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Reports, 1979-1997 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Minutes, 1963-1975 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Minutes, 1975-1985 (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Minutes, 1986-1994 (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Minutes, 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Benefits Plan Committee - Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Medical Care, 1960-1994 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Matching Gifts, 1987-2012 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Matching Gifts - Supplementary Material (Box 258, Folder 2)
    Acknowledgement letters.
  - Personnel - Personnel Action Notices (PAN), 1996 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Staff Manuals, 1988 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Staff Manuals, 1992-2006 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    Including field staff
  - Personnel - Brown Bag Series, 1991-2009 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - RF Flex Benefits package, 1997-2013 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Learning Officers, 2001-2014 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Learning and Liaison Unit, 2001-2004 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Management Training, 2001-2008 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Orientation, 1997-2010 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Employee Assistance Program (EAP), 2002-2009 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Staff Reduction Program, 2002 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - Human Resources - Voluntary Separation Program, 2006 (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Diversity and Inclusion Program, 2012-2013 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - Performance Management Process, 2012 (Box 262, Folder 5)
- Social Sciences, 910; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Program and Policy - Third World, 1986-1998 (Box 263, Folder 1)
- Publicity and Publications, 912; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
  - Publications, 1980-1999 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Publications - Supplementary Material, 1980-1981 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Publications - Consultants - A-Z, 1997-1999 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Publications - In House - RF Connect, 2002-2004 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Publications - In House - RockIt, 1998 (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Publications - In House - Employee Bulletin, 1998-2014 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Publications - In House - Rockfiles, 1998-2013 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Publications - In House - Rockfiles, 1998-2013 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Publications - "Why Things Work", 1988-1989 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Publicity, 1997-1998 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, 1997-1998 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Publications - Trustee Newsletter (Pub-4), 1975-1980 (Box 386, Folder 5)
  - Rock-1 - Press Releases, Vol 12, 1970 (Box 387, Folder 1)
  - NL - Staff Program News, 1970-1972 (Box 387, Folder 2)
  - RF - The RF Insider, 1973-1977 (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - Rock-1 - Press Releases, Vol 13, 1974-1979 (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Rock-1 - Press Releases, Vol 14, 1980 (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Rock-2 - RF Illustrated, 1972-1977 (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Rock-2 - RF Illustrated, 1986 (Box 388, Folder 2)
- Service Departments, 914; 22.41 Cubic Feet 59 letter document boxes
  - Administrative Team, 2002 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Central Analysis Unit, 1988-1991 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Communications Office, 1986-2003 (Box 266, Folder 2-4, Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Communications Office, 2004-2011 (Box 268, Folder 2-3)
  - Communications Office, 2012-2014 (Box 269, Folder 1-3)
  - Communications Office, 2012-2014 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Communications Office - Supplementary Material (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Communications Office - Front of File, 1997-2003 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Communications Office - Front of File, 2004-2013 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Communications Office - Photo Releases, 2001-2005 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Communications Office - Service Agreements (Not Consultants), 1996-2006 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Communications Office - Rocklink, 1999-2011 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - Communications Office - Rocklink, 1999-2011 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Communications Office - Records and Information Management (RIM), 2012-2014 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Communications Office - Press Releases, 2006-2011 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - Comptrollers Office, 1981-2003 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Comptrollers Office - Permanently Restricted
  - Comptrollers Office - Consultancy Action Closings, 1996-1998 (Box 271, Folder 4, Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Comptrollers Office - Consultancy Action Closings, 1999-2000 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Comptrollers Office - Consultancy Action Closings, 2001-2003 (Box 273, Folder 1-2)
  - Comptrollers Office - Consultancy Action Closings, 2004-2006 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Comptrollers Office - Miscellaneous Grant Acknowledgements, 1994 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Comptrollers Office - Expenditure Responsibility Grantees, 2003 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Investments Office, 2007-2009 (Box 274, Folder 4)
    Restricted - Investments Office - Permanently Restricted
  - Presidents Office - Videos and Photographs, 2007-2014 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Open in 2035
  - Office of Grants Management, 2006-2014 (Box 276, Folder 1-2)
  - Computer Services Department, 1980-1997 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Financial Resources, 2003-2015 (Box 277, Folder 1-3)
    Restricted - Treasurer - Open in 2036
  - Information Technology Department, 1997-2014 (Box 278, Folder 1-2)
    Restricted - Information Technology - Open in 2035
  - Library and Research Services, 2004-2008 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - Library and Research Services, 2004-2008 (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - Office of Grants Management - Search Meetings Blog, 2007 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - Office Service, 1980-1987 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Personnel/Property - Open in 2058
  - Office Service, 1988-2014 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Personnel/Property - Open in 2085
  - Office Service - Supplementary Material (Box 280, Folder 2, Box 281, Folder 1-2)
  - Office of Vice President and General Counsel, 2006-2015 (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
    Restricted - General Counsel - Permanently Restricted
  - Office of Vice President and General Counsel - Subpoenas (Rangel), 2009-2015 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Presidents Office, 2005-2012 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Presidents Office - Trips, Meetings, Events, 2004-2009 (Box 283, Folder 3, Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS), 1922-1975 (Box 285, Folder 1-3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS), 1975-1989 (Box 285, Folder 4-5, Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS), 1990-2004 (Box 286, Folder 2-3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS), 1990-2004 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Declinations Management, 1992-2003 (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Copyright, 1986-2010 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Electronic Records Management, 1997-2000 (Box 287, Folder 2-3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Electronic Records Management - Supplementary Material (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Bellagio, 1970-1987 (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Malawi, 1991-1998 (Box 288, Folder 3-4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Malawi, 1988-2000 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Mexico, 1991-2004 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Nairobi, 1971-2001 (Box 289, Folder 3-4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Nairobi, 2001-2011 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - New Orleans, 2007 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Thailand, 2000 (Box 290, Folder 3)